(Leonard:)Whatever.
(Leonard:)- You have to do something about it.
- Why?
(Leonard:)Because she's your sister.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Sheldon:)Yes, we shared a uterus
for nine months.
(Sheldon:)But since then, we've pretty much gone
our own separate ways.
Okay, consider this.
(Leonard:)With your father gone,
it is your responsibility...
(Leonard:)...to make sure
that Missy chooses a suitable mate.
(Sheldon:)I hadn't considered that.
(Sheldon:)We do share DNA.
(Sheldon:)So there is the possibility,
however remote...
(Sheldon:)...that resting in her loins
is the potential for another individual...
(Sheldon:)...as remarkable as myself.
(Leonard:)Exactly. And you owe it to yourself
and to posterity...
(Leonard:)...to protect the genetic integrity
of your sister's future offspring.
(Sheldon:)You're right. If someone wants
to get at Missy's fallopian tubes...
(Sheldon:)...they'll have to go through me.